<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

<string id="military_trader_who">
		<text>Holy smoke! And who are you? Answer me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_trader_about">
		<text>Curb your enthusiasm, a stalker, I ... Trader. Call me "Military Trader". Who I really am, it's not your bussines ... I have to say, I'm not interested with your relationship with military and other stalker's clan's .I trade gear and equipment of the military. Oh yeah, one more thing, you can find trader like me , don't afraid they have nothing personal with their clan enemies , they traders just like me! Well, we'll be busy with it or how?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_trader_buy">
		<text>Will.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_trader_0">
		<text>Hi man, you must be a "merchant", true?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_trader_1">
		<text>Well ... so if you want it, then "yes. " . I'm selling them weapons, equipment, and sometimes all sorts of rubbish, which my mates bring to me. Don't be confused with my neutrality - we have deal that merchant are not conflicting with other clan's.About bandits they protect me, and I give them equipment and provision. Got it? So, you're in case? Take what you want, and get out of here. I'm don't wanna see your fancy face anymore</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_trader_2">
		<text>In the case, in the case.</text>
	</string>

      <string id="merc_trader_lc_info_0">
		<text>Listen, tell me how to get here at the Wild Territory?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_lc_info_1">
		<text>At the Wild Territory is best to get through the dead city, I'll send the coordinates to your PDA. By this way, you will be going on mercs teritory, beware of snipers in the city!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_0">
		<text>Hello, mercenary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_1">
		<text>I am not a mercenary, and you know it, if not, then go down to my ... Hmm ... colleagues, they explain to you. I suggest that products of mercenaries, you are interested in something, stalker?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_2">
		<text>Yes, of course.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monlit_trader_lc_info_0">
		<text>You're here, you see, long ago! Not podskazhesh any way shortly, with the radar in the south zone? And then through the warehouses do not always want to walk, not quiet there ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_lc_info_1">
		<text>Prompt, I'm interested in keeping customers, heh, heh! Areas to the south there are two paths: one will lead you to the dark valley, and the other at Jantar - dangerous place here, so you should strictly surveyors stake! Will a huckster, passed on my regards!</text>
		<action>ogsm_freeplay.set_lc6_rad_xy</action>
	</string>

	<string id="monlit_trader_0">
		<text>You must be a trader Monolith?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_1">
		<text>It is true stalker. I Sell the equipment group Monolith. About how I was allowed to stay here, do not even ask. Just hint that Monolith - not those "fanatics" that they seem. They have their own ... patrons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_2">
		<text>And what about radiation? Radar immediately at hand!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_3">
		<text>I have a special hat from the "friends" of the hill. Do not try to force me away - he still self-destruct as soon as you try to remove it, at the same time and you will tear off your hands. Oh believe me, its technology "friends" know how to defend. By the way, my ... employer has asked me to tell you that you have been careful reactor. He is with you may contact, and yet asked me to convey: "Not everything that we obviously is indeed the case ..."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_4">
		<text>Fuck you all make out!</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
