<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

<string id="military_trader_who">
		<text>Holy shoot! And who are you? Answer me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_trader_about">
		<text>Curb your enthusiasm, stalker, I am... A trader. Call me "Military Trader". Who I really am, is not of your concern... I have to say, I'm not interested in your relationship with the military and other stalker clans .I trade gear and equipment of the military. Oh yeah, one more thing, you may meet other traders like me , don't be afraid: they have nothing against their clan enemies , they're traders just like me! Well, we're going to do business or what?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_trader_buy">
		<text>Let's get to business.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_trader_0">
		<text>Hi man, you must be a "merchant", is that true?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_trader_1">
		<text>Well ... if you want it, then "yes". I'm selling weapons, equipment, and sometimes all sorts of rubbish my mates bring to me. Don't be confused with my neutrality - we have a deal that merchants are not conflicting any other clans. About bandits... They protect me, and I give them equipment and provision. Got it? So, are you in? Take what you want, and get out of here. I don't wanna see your fancy face just for chit-chat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_trader_2">
		<text>Ok, I'm in.</text>
	</string>

      <string id="merc_trader_lc_info_0">
		<text>Listen, can you tell me how to get from here to the Wild Territory?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_lc_info_1">
		<text>The best way to the Wild Territory is through the Dead City, I'll send the coordinates to your PDA. It's the mercs territory, so beware of snipers in the city!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_0">
		<text>Hello, mercenary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_1">
		<text>I am not a mercenary, and you know it, if you don't - then go down to my ... Hmm ... colleagues, and they will explain it to you. I offer some mercenaries' stuff, you are interested in something, stalker?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_trader_2">
		<text>Yes, of course I am.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monlit_trader_lc_info_0">
		<text>You've been here for long, I suppose! Can you prompt me any shorter way from the Radar to the south of the Zone? I wouldn't like to take the path through the warehouses all the time, it's not quiet there...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_lc_info_1">
		<text>Sure I can, I'm interested in keeping my customers alive, heh, heh! There are two paths to the southern areas: one will lead you to the Dark Valley, and the other to Jantar - dangerous place there, so you should strictly watch out! By the way, when you see the Huckster, give him my regards!</text>
		<action>ogsm_freeplay.set_lc6_rad_xy</action>
	</string>

	<string id="monlit_trader_0">
		<text>You must be a trader of Monolith?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_1">
		<text>It is true stalker. I sell the equipment for and of Monolith Worshippers. About how I was allowed to stay here, do not even ask. Just a hint: that Monolith followers are not quite those "fanatics" that they seem. They have their own ... patrons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_2">
		<text>And what about Radar's emission? The Radar is just "next door" from here!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_3">
		<text>I have a special balaclava from the "friends" among the "big wigs" here. Do not try to take it from me by force though - it will self-destruct as soon as you try to remove it, additionally tearing off your hands. Oh, believe me, "friends" know how to defend their technology. By the way, my ... employer has asked me to tell you that you should be careful near the reactor. He may contact you himself in future, and yet he asked me to convey his message to you: "Not everything that seems obvious to us is obvious indeed"...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monlit_trader_4">
		<text>Fuck you all! I'll make it out!</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
