<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="talk_about_psy_emission">
		<text>Well, the strongest known sources of such radiation are two: notorious burner Brains and the territory of the plant "germ. "
		Therefore, in these places zombie stalkers occurs most.
		Rumor has it that the plant is another powerful source, and like he is the cause of the Psi-emission. But nobody ever goes there, so believe it or not, decide.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_zombied_stalker_1">
		<text>The most fundamental difference lies in their manner of behavior: not disturbed by anything, zombies roam aimlessly from side to side. They can be easily detected at a great distance from the characteristic gait and slurred mumbling. 
During combat, they do not use any tactics to get away from the fire or shelter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_1">
		<text>Instead of lost reason they have quickly evolved animal instincts that allow to survive in a zone. As a result, following the ejection of mutations, these are already the animals, not only
survived, but have adapted to new conditions, acquired a new quality.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_2">
		<text>- common to all beings Zones regenerative, carnivores and, of course, exacerbated by night vision. 
Initially, more than strong legs are transformed into the hind limb with the unique mobility of the ankle, allowing these creatures, because of 
source of anatomical features, slow-moving at 4 limbs, to make significant leaps and allows you to apply 
significant damage, again, beating the hindquarters.</text> 
  	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_3">
		<text>vorite habitat Snork - a highly radioactive areas of land,
usually located close to the so-called "brain burner", apparently giving
that there are advantages in hunting big game, and unfortunately, people.
Meet Snork and in artificial burrows - the cellars, the ruins.
\nSnork population clearly increases as one approaches the center of the Zone, on the periphery
as a rule, they get less.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_4">
		<text>- Chernobyl dogs - definitely not, because though Snork and animals, but the alpha 
  biocurrents brain waves they were human, not the same as those 
  at Chernobyl dogs. 
- Controllers. A complex question. At the periphery of habitat Snork and controllers 
  not intersect, and we were unable to find Snork driven controllers. 
  As we approach the center of the Zone in Pripyat for example, the density of the mutated 
  organisms increases, and this situation is possible. The whole question is, 
  enough in the brains of these animals remained a "human framework" for 
  psy-connect to it by the Controller of the brain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_5">
		<text>-But there are many mysteries associated with Snork.
		- Why all Snork - mask Burtz and Holster?
- Why all the individuals have similar damage to the ridge?
- in general, why they are so much alike? (noise in the hall) 
- why, once these creatures have no way of reproduction - not females - they are still
  not destroy the other inhabitants of the Zone? 
- how much they were, these victims of the liquidators, which served as "raw material"
  for Snork? (noise in the hall is enhanced) 
- and, most importantly, someone saw the corpse Snork a week ago? (silence in the hall)
  at least a bone? or parts of the body?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_snork_6">
		<text>-I think that is so similar to each other Snork - is any duplicate of the original sample. Where he came from - is another question. The fact that they are descended from people - no doubt.
If there is a reason for the appearance of such duplicates, or clones of these creatures, then until we eliminate this mysterious source of their reproduction, we can not destroy them Nikodym ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_1">
		<text>The reason for their appearance is unknown, as the reason for the appearance of most monsters. It is surprisingly moving creature. And yet - surprisingly tenacious and vicious, just gripping, has not let go. Or her, or she is. A pressure jaw chimeras, I'm sorry, is comparable with the pressure of good industrial press ... Chimera kills all indiscriminately. Even if not hungry. 
A hungry chimera becomes even more dangerous and attacks even on other chimeras, and not disdaining carrion. "The favorite" food for her is the meat of wild boars mutants and, unfortunately, man ... She has something feline, swift, silent.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_2">
		<text>After each sudden movement of the chimera brief stops in total immobility, is dissolved in the surrounding landscape, and go try to understand - whether imagined that, then if the wind suddenly into the bushes ... 
If you do not know what to look for, what to look out, you risk to find a chimera at a moment when she picked up to you on the minimum distance pripadet to land the last jump.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_3">
		<text>You see, the behavior of this creature is so unpredictable that it can neither understand nor explain. At one time I tried to study chimeras. But very soon realized that nothing will come of it. Although it had two heads, but when we tried to establish contact with them, felt that the minds of these goals alone and was somewhere else. 
Each chimera has unique inherent qualities to her alone. Therefore, even the most careful observation of one of the individuals did not provide for understanding the other. In addition, as I said, chimeras flatly refuse to go on contact. 
Perhaps it is only generated by the Zone being endowed with intelligence, with which it is impossible to make contact, even at the most primitive level.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_4">
		<text>Outwardly no different from normal chimeras, the chimera is capable of electric
briefly to create around himself a powerful electric shock that hits
all living within a radius of 5.2 meters and, due to the high saturation of the soil zone
abnormal electricity that causes fatal damage in a radius of about
15-20 meters.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_5">
		<text>The rate of decay of charge in the vertical is much higher than the horizontal and, presumably, falls to relatively safe values ??are already at an altitude of more than 3-4 meters. Naturally, when precipitation and
especially in the thunderstorm, the situation has changed (deteriorated).
\nKnowledge of this feature allowed some hunting to survive after the collision with the chimera of electricity. As a rule, they managed to kill a monster
High rocks, buildings, etc. by fifty (!) armor-piercing bullets or
3-4x well-aimed shots from a grenade launcher in the head monster.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_about_chimera_6">
		<text>Characteristically, in the gastrointestinal tract chimeras sometimes find artifacts
hunters called "bun. " Will express a bold hypothesis that eating such
artifacts and transforms ordinary chimera chimera in electrical.  
\nExplore the power generating agencies of chimeras in the lab and remove
the exact characteristics of the generated electric field has not yet been
possible, as yet nobody has been able to catch the creature,
and delivered by the hunters body for understandable reasons are in very poor condition, simply put - "sieve".</text>
	</string>
<string id="talk_about_krovosos_1">
<text>Although the bloodsucking heard everything, not so much fortunate, who were still alive after a meeting with them. I myself have seen them only in photos. 
But the stories of these lucky ones, vampire 
represents a high-stooped humanoid creature with many tentacles in 
area of the mouth, sometimes covered with short hair. Apparently, these mutants prefer 
solitary, although sometimes there are groups consisting of several 
individuals. Trying to settle in uninhabited areas, such as: caves, wet basements 
and abandoned buildings. Bloodsuckers can be found in the vicinity of SRI Agroprom, 
the catacombs of the institute, in a dark valley, on the Wild Territory and of course a sad 
well-known village at the army warehouses, nicknamed stalkers "village bloodsuckers." 
Its distinctive ability to become virtually invisible, they can use 
Hunting and camouflage, trying to sneak up unnoticed by the victim to cause her 
deathblow muscular, equipped with sharp claws paw.</text>
</string>
<string id="talk_about_krovosos_2">
<text>Stalker, who comes up with blood-suckers, it is important to distinguish two types of its behavior - Attack 
and resting state. In the first, the most common case, it is necessary to determine 
Outgoing, threats, and then be ready to open fire. 
Most effective to target a monster right between the eyes, because their luminosity, they 
give the location of the bloodsucker, while he remains invisible. It is also important not 
panic, do not attempt to escape, you know, vampire catches up with you. When 
the second scenario, the mutant is unaware of your presence. Appropriate to deviate 
only in their footsteps, but if you are confident in their abilities, it is best to protect themselves and 
his brothers-stalkers shot bloodsucker accurate shot in the head with enough 
powerful weapons.</text>
</string>
<string id="talk_about_krovosos_3">
<text>Undamaged in the battle tentacles bloodsucker is an interesting subject for study, 
and the rarity of this product ensures a stable price for scientists. Most likely, this 
modified mouthparts - tongue, cheek and jaw. With their help, bloodsucker 
nourished, leaving their victims only dried, resembling a mummy wrapper. 
In conclusion, I would say that it is not necessary to record themselves in the dead at the meeting 
with bloodsuckers, because if you know its strengths and weaknesses, it is quite possible to go from 
victory. Good luck to you, stalker!</text>
</string>
<string id="talk_about_plaque_rat_1">
<text>"plague rat" - is mutated lab rats who have escaped from the vivarium (which is why there are, basically, in the laboratory of X-18).
As a result of experiments in rats was changed brain tissue, in which the flies were grown mutants.</text>
</string>
<string id="talk_about_plaque_rat_2">
<text>Flies - vectors of gene causing the mutation of the brain, ie, prepares the place with the most favorable conditions for larval development, as a consequence leads to the destruction of the brain and psevdosmerti.
There also carried out tests on effects of flies on the person (zombie - carriers of the larvae of flies). The experiment was brought to the end was not the brain, without any additional processing complex radiation, rejects the eggs of flies. 
Flies themselves, at this stage, can cause multiple wounds, which cause profuse bleeding and infection. The name "plague rat" comes from the name of "The Plague century XXI".
</text>
</string>
<!--Kruglov i Semenov rasskazyvayut o zone-->
<string id="talk_about_horrortime_1">
<text>Well, listen. For the Zone is appropriate to say that in her relatively long periods of stability alternate with short periods of instability (and possible subsequent ejection time of terror). 
Period of instability differ changing anomalies, artifacts, active changes in the activity of monsters. 
If during this period appears a number of unstable (short lived) Education: phantoms and moving anomalies, this time called "time of terror." Because during the horror is changing the psi anomalies born phantoms, subjecting the inhabitants of the zone psychic shock and horror during the stalkers suffer dizziness and hallucinations, then this period is also called the "psi-emissions." 
Part of the entities that appear during the terror disappear without a trace to the end. </text>
</string>
<string id="talk_about_horrortime_2">
<text>Right. Movable anomalies occur when the disappearing old and new anomalies. Thus, moving the anomaly - it is an intermediate stage of transition of all the anomalies of a stable distribution to another.
Therefore, moving anomalies are also unstable and often disappear by the end of time terror.</text>
</string>

<string id="talk_about_horrortime_3">
<text>Phantoms - is the result of the interaction of the psi-field and consciousness. And scientists with Amber found out that the effectiveness of birth phantoms and their shape depend on the mental state of man.
Part of the phantoms can see most of the stalkers, but some part can be seen only by one man and, apparently, is a product of his mind.
</text>
</string>

<!--Dialogi s odinochkami na Svalke-->
<string id="stalker_garbage_1">
<text>The zone spans a stronger drug. Sit in the waiting room (at the cordon, so) a week and all - to start something gnawing inside, demand again to walk on the very brink, in which the end, death. 
And well, if by that time was a customer, and the Zone is not going away just because you can not without it, but in a case that will bring profit. 
Actually because of the profit, mostly here and find yourself. Artifacts previously brought a lot of money. Not to say that the lungs, but still. 
Here people matereyut, transformed from a tourist stalkers and there is even such that gradually forget about the profits, getting pleasure from the dangers and all new, that is inherent in the Zone.</text>
</string>
<string id="stalker_garbage_2">
<text>Many still live now hunting for artifacts, although the money they now have less to bear.</text>
</string>
<string id="stalker_garbage_3">
<text>Initially, the scientists bombarded with orders, private collectors hired military and also hung on all vestibule around the area, buying up all that took out the stalkers. 
Now it is more difficult. Of course, after the release artifacts appeared in the Zone, but many of them are almost not worth the risk to which they dig. 
They are the scientists and collectors have already accumulated a considerable amount, and the law of supply and demand took its. Such artifacts as a "quirk", "Medusa" and others like them have already bought up almost for nothing, and experienced stalkers they have not even picked up, leaving the newcomers - let the joy and climb deep into the zone. 
New to the depth of the zone - the corpse. Proved Zone.</text>
</string>
<string id="stalker_garbage_4">
<text>Collect of course. "Battery," "Gingerbread Man" and other serednyachki is still decent stand, and they do not shun anyone, but to find a "soul" - this is a rare stroke of luck. Scientists are still klyanchat this artifact, but rarely anyone from the stalkers were lucky to find at least two "Souls" 
and only found only a fool would sell - and most will fit. And for good money possible for scientists in the lab Sakharov make a very expensive and the required artifacts artificial - transmutation. But there still should get.</text>
</string>
</string_table>
